mypayingcryptoads.com 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy - MyPayingCryptoAds.com

**MyPayingCryptoAds Privacy and Data Policy**

**Introduction:** [MyPayingCryptoAds.com](http://mypayingcryptoads.com/) (“MPCA”) has extreme commitment to providing excellent service to all of our members, affiliates and customers, including respecting their concerns about privacy. We understand that visitors to our website may have questions about how this website collects and uses information. We have prepared this statement to inform you of the privacy principles that govern [MyPayingCryptoAds.com](http://mypayingcryptoads.com/).

This statement contains numerous general and technical details about the steps we take to respect your privacy concerns. The bottom line is that meeting your needs and expectations form the foundation of everything we do - including protecting your privacy.

For the purpose of Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA) 2012 in Republic of Singapore ([http://statutes.agc.gov.sg](http://statutes.agc.gov.sg/)), the data controller is [MyPayingCryptoAds.com](http://mypayingcryptoads.com/). By visiting this website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy and Data Policy.

**1\. Information we Gather and Track**

1.1 We may collect and process the following data about you:

1.1.1 When we need to collect personally identifiable information from you, we will ask you to voluntarily supply us with the information we need. For example, if you would like to create a MPCA account or receive information regarding upcoming MPCA business advances, we will ask you for information such as name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, personal description, documents and photograph.

1.1.2 Information we collect about you. With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information:

1.1.2.1 An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you browse the Internet. When users request a page from our site, our servers log the user's current IP address. We use Internet address (IP address) of the computer or device you use to access your MPCA account, in order to help detect possible instances of unauthorized access to your account.

1.1.2.2 This website does not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse the site. This means that, unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us with personally identifiable information, we will not know your name, your e-mail address, or any other personally identifiable information.

1.1.3 Our website uses cookie technology. Cookies are strings of text that a website may store on a user's computer. Our website uses cookies but only requires them in the online reservation process. Cookies enable our website to keep track of your preferences and activities relating to the website. Our website creates session cookies for each visit in order to facilitate your visit. The session cookie expires at the end of the session.

1.1.3.1 Use of Cookies and E-Mails - We use a third party service provider to send marketing e-mails on behalf of MPCA. There are no cookies in the e-mail. However, when an e-mail recipient click on a link to The MPCA website included in the e-mail, a persistent cookie is placed on the user's computer. This cookie is used to measure the effectiveness of our e-mail marketing efforts and better understand how our users navigate through the site. The cookie set by our service provider will remain on your hard drive 30 days after the last time you clicked on the coded link in the e-mail, or until you delete it.

1.1.3.2 Use of Cookies for Advertising - We use third party service providers to serve and host our advertisements. These third parties use persistent cookies to track the number of times our site is accessed and whether the site was accessed from the advertisement. The cookies generated from the advertisements do not contain personally identifiable information and may remain on your hard drive three or more years unless deleted by you.

1.1.3.3 The third party service providers mentioned above are contractually bound not to use any information they gather for any purpose other than providing services to us. Cookies do not corrupt or damage your computer or computer files. In addition, we do not use cookies to gather information concerning your visits to non-MPCA websites. If you do not wish to receive these cookies, you may set your browser to reject the cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so may affect your ability to perform certain transactions on our website.

**2\. Information Sharing**  

2.1 MPCA strictly follows Knowing your Clients (KYC) policy to meet compliance requirement. Knowing your Clients (KYC) is legal requirement from Monetary Authority of Singapore Notice 626 on Prevention of Money Laundering and Countering the Financing of Terrorism. To meet this obligation we will request and store personal documents in secure servers.

2.2 We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

2.3 We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as ID verification.

2.4 We may also disclose your personal information:

2.4.1 as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or a similar legal process

2.4.2 when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request

2.4.3 If MPCA is involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as the choices you may have regarding the sharing of your personal information

2.4.4 To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**3\. User Access and Choice**

3.1 If your personal information changes, or if you wish to discontinue the use of our service, you may correct, delete, update, amend or request to deactivate your account by emailing our Customer Support at [admin@mypayingcryptoads.com](mailto:admin@mypayingcryptoads.com) or by raising a supprt ticket. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

3.2 We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with service. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

3.3 If you wish to subscribe to our mailing list(s), we will use your name and email address to send the information to you. Respecting your right to privacy, we will remove you from our mailing lists should you wish to stop receiving our updates or marketing emails by contacting our support team.

**4\. Storage of Personal Data**

4.1 MPCA handles your customer information with high standards of information security. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with national regulations to guard your non public personal information.

4.2 The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the Republic of Singapore. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the Singapore who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. MPCA will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

4.3 All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted [using SSL technology]. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

4.3.1 The security of your MPCA account also relies on your protection of your MPCA password. You should not share your MPCA password with anyone. MPCA representatives will never ask you for your password, so any e-mail or other communication requesting your password should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious.

4.3.2 If you do share your MPCA password with a third party for any reason, including third party promises of providing you additional services such as account aggregation, the third party will have access to your account and your personal information, and you may be responsible for actions taken using your password.

4.3.3 If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account at MPCA. If you have any further concerns please contact our support team as soon as possible.

4.4 Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**5\. Privacy on Age Limit**

5.1 This website does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18.

5.2 If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 18 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe we have received any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please contact us at [admin@mypayingcryptoads.com](mailto:admin@mypayingcryptoads.com).

**6\. Additional Policy Information**

6.1 Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of MPCA. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

6.2 We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [admin@mypayingcryptoads.com](mailto:admin@mypayingcryptoads.com).

**7\. Privacy Policy Effective Date**

7.1 The privacy policy is in effect at the time of each visit to our site. Please check our privacy policy each time you visit our website if you are concerned about how your information will be used.

**8\. Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

8.1 We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this website prior to any changes being effectuated. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information regarding our privacy practices.

**9\. Contact Information**

9.1 You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at [admin@mypayingcryptoads.com](mailto:admin@mypayingcryptoads.com)
